An, Nguyen Thien

Senior Marketing Manager

Work experience

SENIOR MARKETING MANAGER Spiral Consulting Co. 27B Nguyen Dinh Chieu, D1 / Since October 2022

Type of business: Recruitment & Staffing Agency, Consultation

In charge of planning, monitoring & executing periodical marketing plans to recuit qualified candidates (fieldforce) for clients: Unilever, Samsung, Abbott, Pepsico, Cocacola, Vinamilk, Aqua, Daikin, Johnson & Johnson...

HIGHLIGHT

- Staff Quant.: 12 staffs (Marketing, Designer, Intern) 02 Independent Team*
- Key Achievement: Contribution to Raw Candidate Source 70%, Qualified Candidate by Internal 30 - 45%, Successful Candidate to Clients 30 - 35%

Marketing Activities

- + Lead the Team to plan, execute, and manage the marketing campaigns with appropriate channels: Facebook/Instagram Ads, Google AdWords to generate qualified Leads (Candidates) for our clients and build branding activities for the company (B2B)
- + Organize & run monthly events such as: Job Fairs, Training attract & increase the quality of candidate sources
- + Conduct designs of the company profile/brochure & pitching presentations
- + Support the internal employee branding activities: idea brainstorming, internal design, event planning & execution, photoshoot & filming,...
- + Manage the Team to produce 20 25 posts/day on social media such as: Facebook/Instagram, Tiktok, Zalo...

• Marketing Department Build & Coaching

- + Submit an efficient Org. Chart to build up a comprehensive marketing department with neccessarry functions
- + Training & Coaching to improve staffs' performance from begining

• Website Development

- + Directly work with agency to build up Recruitment & Corporate Websites from srcatch
- + Improve candidate behavior in applying job

SENIOR DIGITAL MARKETING MANAGER Embassy Education 21 Pham Ngoc Thach, District 3,

HCMC / From February 2020 to June 2022

Type of business: Education, Consultation

In charge of planning, monitoring & executing periodical digital marketing plans & PR activities to promote 12 belonging brands: pre-school, elementary school, afterschool (music, dance, yoga, early childhood education, acting, visual arts...)

HIGHLIGHT

- Staff Quant.: 7 staffs (Digital, Content, Intern)
- Key Achievement: Qualified Lead reach 70%

Digital Marketing

- + Lead the Digital Team to plan, execute, and manage the digital marketing campaigns with appropriate channels: Facebook/Instagram Ad, Google AdWords (Keyword, GDN, Youtube ad), LinkedIn, Zalo Ad, Email Marketing, Seeding, Digital Display Banner
- + Worked toward Lead Generation Campaigns such as admission recruitment, participant recruitment for workshops & launching events, students for online classes
- + Created periodical analytical reports with highlighted insight to evaluate the campaign efficiency

• Social Media Development

- + Managed the Team to create monthly content direction, produce appropriate daily content for each social media platform
- + Worked with the Video Production, Designers for the excellent materials which helped to increase the organic Reach, Engagement, Page Likes/Followers...

• Website Development

- + Worked directly with the development team (UI/UX Design & Coder) to build up Websites (at least 3 websites per year & 4 Microsites/Landing Pages per month), Plug-in updates, & website
- + Managed SEO Agency to plan & execute SEO activities & ensure the top position of the chosen keywords

Management

- + Built up the Team with high self-discipline, proactive, flexible & strong specialized skills with other Teams
- + Created collaboration process & template system for better internal & external team working result



abla

53/19/33 Street 8, Truong
Thanh Ward, District 9, HCM

C

About me

10-year experience in developing, implementing & managing marketing strategies with the outstanding abilities to understand the ongoing market scenario and customers trends using exceptional marketing communications skills.

Skills

Facebook

Facebook Ad Manager. Facebook Business Manager, Content Development Strategy

Google AdWords

Keyword, GDN, Youtube Ad

Other Paid Ad Platforms

LinkedIn Ads, Zalo Ads, Coc Coc Ads. Tik Tok Ads

Related

Google Analytics, Google Search Console, Get Response, Mail Chimp, WordPress, Wufoo...

Other skills

Stragegic Planning

Social Media Content

Website & SEO

Events & Offline

Work experience

MARKETING MANAGER Soul Corporation 214 Pasteur, District 3, HCMC / 2017

Type of business: Education, Entertainment, Music & Performing Art Hub (English Speaking Environment)

In charge of planning, monitoring periodically marketing plans to promote Soul Music & Performing Arts Academy, Soul Live Project **HIGHLIGHT**

- Staff Quant.: 7 staffs (Marketing, Designer, Event)
- Key Achievement: increase 250% new Lead, conversion rate to Qualified Lead 35%; form an
 efficient Org. Chart for Marketing Department

Marketing Activities

- + Plan, allocate & carry out day to day marketing duties & campaigns to achieve KPI following the target of new lead via Facebook Ad, Google AdWord, Partnership, with regular reporting & budget control to Managing Director
- + Mainly in charge of social media management & recruitment events such as Open Day, Workshop, Free trial Class...
- + Prepared the press releases and maximized all PR opportunities for the organization including managing the PR agency, developing key relationships with target media
- + Promoted for ticket selling: Facebook Ads Running, Facebook Group Seeding, Event sites Partners
- Internal Events for Current Students
- + Plan, oganize & manage yearly, monthly internal events such as End of Term Showcase, Recital...: Concept definition, content orientation, designing monitoring
- Website Development & Administration
- + Manage & develop websites of the Corporation, ensured all contents are up to date

MARKETING ACTIVATION MANAGER Vingle Representative Office in Vietnam 54 Dinh Cong

Trang, District 1, HCM / From 2015 to 2017

Type of business: IT, Start-up, Advertising, Community Network, Investment, Consultation, Co-working Space (English Speaking Environment)

In charge of planning & monitoring marketing strategies to promote Interest Network (web & app) in Vietnam:

Content Creation - Promotion - User Attraction - Interaction Boosting HIGHLIGHT

- Budget Scale: ~VND100 million/month
- Staff Quant.: 6 staffs (Marketing & Developer), 30 freelancers (Content)
- Key Achievement: 1,000 new user/month, lowest CPC VND30, 200 new content post/day

• Marketing Management Activities

- + Design, implement & evaluate marketing plans to reach KPI by phases under assigned budget in both online & offline: Facebook Ad, Google AdWords, Youtube Ad, CocCoc Ad...
- + Input & monitors taffs' planning & implementing to attract new users & maintain active users on our platforms: minigame, livestream, contest...
- Content Management Activities
- $+ \ Manage\ Team\ to\ create\ content\ on\ our\ platform\ \&\ social\ media\ to\ optimize\ \&\ support\ marketing\ activities$
- Development Management
- + In charge of planning & monitoring ofdeveloping new product projects & business plans which serve the organization's demands under Lean Start-up, Agile strategies
- Business Development Activities
- + Directly work work owners in Vietnam (Admicro, FPT,Netlink, etc.) to deliver monetization on
- HR Supports
- + Generated & supplied HR policy in Vietnam for Korean Director

SENIOR MARKETING EXECUTIVE Quang Minh Clinic Nguyen Kiem, Phu Nhuan / From 2014 to 2015

Type of business: Healthcare, (Percutaneous Laser Disc Decompression, PLDD)

MARKETING EXECUTIVE Wingrate Ly Thuong Kiet, D10 / From 2012 to 2013 Type of business: IT, Website Development

Languages

Vietnamese

Native

English

Proficient

Education

Bachelor of International Relations
- University of Social Sciences &
Humanities - Vietnam National
University of Ho Chi Minh City
2008 - 2012

TOEIC 745 - IIG Vietnam 2012

Certificate of Digital Marketing - Vinalink Academy 2014

Interests

Education

Technology & Startup

Books & Reading

Traveling & Discovery

Handcraft

Healthcare & Green Living